<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<Spell_Tokens>
			<Fire_Bolt>
				<ID type="number">0</ID>
				<circle_token type="number">0</circle_token>
				<cone_token type="number">0</cone_token>
				<measurenumber type="number">0</measurenumber>
				<targettoken type="number">0</targettoken>
			</Fire_Bolt>
			<Mage_Armor>
				<ID type="number">0</ID>
				<circle_token type="number">0</circle_token>
				<cone_token type="number">0</cone_token>
				<measurenumber type="number">0</measurenumber>
				<targettoken type="number">0</targettoken>
			</Mage_Armor>
			<Magic_Missile>
				<ID type="number">0</ID>
				<circle_token type="number">0</circle_token>
				<cone_token type="number">0</cone_token>
				<measurenumber type="number">0</measurenumber>
				<targettoken type="number">0</targettoken>
			</Magic_Missile>
		</Spell_Tokens>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">18</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<alignment type="string">Neutral</alignment>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class></class>
			<recordname></recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d6</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">4</hdused>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<name type="string">Wizard</name>
				<rolls>
					<lvl-001 type="number">6</lvl-001>
					<lvl-002 type="number">4</lvl-002>
					<lvl-003 type="number">6</lvl-003>
					<lvl-004 type="number">4</lvl-004>
				</rolls>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.wizard@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">1</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">0</armor>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">13</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<effectlist>
		</effectlist>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">50</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">100</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">300</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">19</load>
			<max type="number">150</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">5110</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">6500</expneeded>
		<featlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magical Reminiscence</name>
				<prerequisite type="string">The ability to cast at least one spell</prerequisite>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p><i>Prerequisite: The ability to cast at least one spell</i></p>
					<p>In a pinch, you can strain yourself to recall one of your latent spells to your mind. You gain the following benefits:</p>
					<p>-Increase the score of your spellcasting ability by 1, to maximum of 20.</p>
					<p>-At any time, you can add a spell to your list of prepared spells (no action required). This spell must be among the spells you know (spellbook for wizards, class list for other classes). You can then cast the added spell normally, by spending the necessary casting time, components, and spell slot.</p>
					<p>This benefit lasts until you finish a long rest. Every time you use this benefit, you take a level of exhaustion.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arcane Recovery</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to regain some of your magical energy by studying your spellbook. Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your wizard level (rounded up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.</p>
					<p>For example, if you're a 4th-level wizard, you can recover up to two levels worth of spell slots. You can recover either a 2nd-level spell slot or two 1st-level spell slots.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As a student of arcane magic, you have a spellbook containing spells that show the first glimmerings of your true power. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the wizard spell list.</p>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know three cantrips of your choice from the wizard spell list. You learn additional wizard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Wizard table.</p>
					<p><b>Spellbook</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you have a spellbook containing six 1st-level wizard spells of your choice.</p>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Wizard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of wizard spells that are available for you to cast. To do so, choose a number of wizard spells from your spellbook equal to your Intelligence modifier + your wizard level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you're a 3rd-level wizard, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With an Intelligence of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination, chosen from your spellbook. If you prepare the 1st-level spell magic missile, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of wizard spells requires time spent studying your spellbook and memorizing the incantations and gestures you must make to cast the spell: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Intelligence is your spellcasting ability for your wizard spells, since you learn your spells through dedicated study and memorization. You use your Intelligence whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability.</p>
					<p>In addition, you use your Intelligence modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a wizard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a wizard spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell in your spellbook. You don't need to have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use an arcane focus (found in chapter 5) as a spellcasting focus for your wizard spells.</p>
					<p><b>Learning Spells of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>Each time you gain a wizard level, you can add two wizard spells of your choice to your spellbook. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the Wizard table. On your</p>
					<p>adventures, you might find other spells that you can add to your spellbook (see the &quot;Your Spellbook&quot; sidebar).</p>
					<h>Your Spellbook</h>
					<p>The spells that you add to your spellbook as you gain levels reflect the arcane research you conduct on your own, as well as intellectual breakthroughs you have had about the nature of the multiverse. You might find other spells during your adventures. You could discover a spell recorded on a scroll in an evil wizard's chest, for example, or in a dusty tome in an ancient library.</p>
					<p><b><i>Copying a Spell into the book. </i></b>When you find a wizard spell of 1st level or higher, you can add it to your spellbook if it is of a level for which you have spell slots and if you can spare the time to decipher and copy it. The spells copied into a spellbook must be of a spell level the wizard can prepare.</p>
					<p>Copying a spell into your spellbook involves reproducing the basic form of the spell, then deciphering the unique system of notation used by the wizard who wrote it. You must practice the spell until you understand the sounds or gestures required, then transcribe it into your spellbook using your own notation.</p>
					<p>For each level of the spell, the process takes 2 hours and costs 50gp. The cost represents material components you expend as you experiment with the spell to master it, as well as the fine inks you need to record it. Once you have spent this time and money, you can prepare the spell just like your other spells.</p>
					<p><b><i>Replacing the Book. </i></b>You can copy a spell from your own spellbook into another book-for example, if you want to make a backup copy of your spellbook. This is just like copying a new spell into your spellbook, but faster and easier, since you understand your own notation and already know how to cast the spell. You need spend only 1 hour and 10 gp for each level of the copied spell. If you lose your spellbook, you can use the same procedure to transcribe the spells that you have prepared into a new spellbook. Filling out the remainder of your spellbook requires you to find new spells to do so, as normal. For this reason, many wizards keep backup spellbooks in a safe place.</p>
					<p><b><i>The Book's Appearance </i></b>Your spellbook is a unique compilation of spells, with its own decorative flourishes and margin notes. It might be a plain, functional leather volume that you received as a gift from your master, a finely bound gilt-edged tome you found in an ancient library, or even a loose collection of notes scrounged together after you lost your previous spellbook in a mishap.</p>
					<p>A spellbook doesn't contain cantrips.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">School of Transmutation</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You are a student of spells that modify energy and matter. To you, the world is not a fixed thing, but eminently mutable, and you delight in being an agent of change. You wield the raw stuff of creation and learn to alter both physical forms and mental qualities. Your magic gives you the tools to become a smith on reality's forge. Some transmuters are tinkerers and pranksters, turning people into toads and transforming copper into silver for fun and occasional profit. Others pursue their magical studies with deadly seriousness, seeking the power of the gods to make and destroy worlds.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.transmutationsavant2@DD PHB Deluxe">Transmutation Savant</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.minoralchemy2@DD PHB Deluxe">Minor Alchemy</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.transmuter_sstone6@DD PHB Deluxe">Transmuter's Stone</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.shapechanger10@DD PHB Deluxe">Shapechanger</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.mastertransmuter14@DD PHB Deluxe">Master Transmuter</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arcane Tradition</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">1</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 2nd level, you choose an arcane tradition, shaping your practice of magic through one of eight schools: Abjuration, Conjuration, Divination, Enchantment, Evocation, Illusion, Necromancy, Transmutation, or Bladesinging, all detailed in their respective chapters.</p>
					<p>Your choice grants you features at 2nd level and again at 6th, 10th, and 14th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transmutation Savant</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Transmutation</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy a transmutation spell into your spellbook is halved.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Minor Alchemy</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Transmutation</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level when you select this school, you can temporarily alter the physical properties of one nonmagical object, changing it from one substance into another. You perform a special alchemical procedure on one object composed entirely of wood, stone (but not a gemstone), iron, copper, or silver, transforming it into a different one of those materials. For each 10 minutes you spend performing the procedure, you can transform up to 1 cubic foot of material. After 1 hour, or until you lose your concentration (as if you were concentrating on a spell), the material reverts to its original substance.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
		</featurelist>
		<hp>
			<adjust type="number">0</adjust>
			<base type="number">24</base>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">24</total>
			<wounds type="number">4</wounds>
		</hp>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">2</temporary>
			<total type="number">5</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<name type="string">Pendiente materiales, arma, ration</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<name type="string">Charcoal para find familiar 10gp each</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>+1 vs cold climates</p>
				</description>
				<effectlist>
				</effectlist>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ropas de invierno</name>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<effectlist>
				</effectlist>
				<name type="string">Materiales mago</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<effectlist>
				</effectlist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<effectlist>
				</effectlist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<effectlist>
				</effectlist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crossbow, Light</name>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 80/320), loading, two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<effectlist>
				</effectlist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Case, Map Or Scroll</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A component pouch is a small, watertight leather belt pouch that has compartments to hold all the material components and other special items you need to cast your spells, except for those components that have a specific cost (as indicated in a spell's description).</p>
				</description>
				<effectlist>
				</effectlist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Component Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00010>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Draconic</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Dwarvish</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<name type="string">Undercommon</name>
			</id-00006>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">4</level>
		<name type="string">Morgan</name>
		<notes type="string">nivel + stat = prepared spells (L4+4int)\nhp dice roll: 4+6+4</notes>
		<perception type="number">13</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Cantrip</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<uses type="number">6</uses>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Cantrip</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<uses type="number">8</uses>
			</id-00003>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">8</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">AC: 3</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<tknimg type="token"></tknimg>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of cured leather)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature who isn't wearing armor, and a protective magical force surrounds it until the spell ends. The target's base AC becomes 13 + its Dexterity modifier. The spell ends if the target dons armor or if you dismiss the spell as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mage Armor</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<tknimg type="token"></tknimg>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<tknimg type="token"></tknimg>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You hurl a mote of fire at a creature or object within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 fire damage. A flammable object hit by this spell ignites if it isn't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d10 when you reach 5th level (2d10), 11th level (3d10), and 17th level (4d10).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Cantrip</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fire Bolt</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">cold</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">(speed -10)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A frigid beam of blue-white light streaks toward a creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, it takes 1d8 cold damage, and its speed is reduced by 10 feet until the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>The spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Cantrip</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ray of Frost</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a firefly or phosphorescent moss)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one object that is no larger than 10 feet in any dimension. Until the spell ends, the object sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. The light can be colored as you like. Completely covering the object with something opaque blocks the light. The spell ends if you cast it again or dismiss it as an action.</p>
					<p>If you target an object held or worn by a hostile creature, that creature must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw to avoid the spell.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Cantrip</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Light</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 hour</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (10 gp worth of charcoal, incense, and herbs that must be consumed by fire in a brass brazier)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain the service of a familiar, a spirit that takes an animal form you choose: bat, cat, crab, frog (toad), hawk, lizard, octopus, owl, poisonous snake, fish (quipper), rat, raven, sea horse, spider, or weasel. Appearing in an unoccupied space within range, the familiar has the statistics of the chosen form, though it is a celestial, fey, or fiend (your choice) instead of a beast.</p>
					<p>Your familiar acts independently of you, but it always obeys your commands. In combat, it rolls its own initiative and acts on its own turn. A familiar can't attack, but it can take other actions as normal.</p>
					<p>When the familiar drops to 0 hit points, it disappears, leaving behind no physical form. It reappears after you cast this spell again</p>
					<p>While your familiar is within 100 feet of you, you can communicate with it telepathically. Additionally, as an action, you can see through your familiar's eyes and hear what it hears until the start of your next turn, gaining the benefits of any special senses that the familiar has. During this time, you are deaf and blind with regard to your own senses.</p>
					<p>As an action, you can temporarily dismiss your familiar. It disappears into a pocket dimension where it awaits your summons. Alternatively, you can dismiss it forever. As an action while it is temporarily dismissed, you can cause it to reappear in any unoccupied space within 30 feet of you.</p>
					<p>You can't have more than one familiar at a time. If you cast this spell while you already have a familiar, you instead cause it to adopt a new form. Choose one of the forms from the above list. Your familiar transforms into the chosen creature.</p>
					<p>Finally, when you cast a spell with a range of touch, your familiar can deliver the spell as if it had cast the spell. Your familiar must be within 100 feet of you, and it must use its reaction to deliver the spell when you cast it. If the spell requires an attack roll, you use your attack modifier for the roll.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Find Familiar (owl) (R)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">AC: 3</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 reaction, which you take when you are hit by an attack or targeted by the magic missile spell</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>An invisible barrier of magical force appears and protects you. Until the start of your next turn, you have a +3 bonus to AC, including against the triggering attack, and you take no damage from magic missile.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield (r)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of pork rind or butter)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Slick grease covers the ground in a 10-foot square centered on a point within range and turns it into difficult terrain for the duration.</p>
					<p>When the grease appears, each creature standing in its area must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or fall prone. A creature that enters the area or ends its turn there must also succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or fall prone.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Grease</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Briefly surrounded by silvery mist, you teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space that you can see.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Misty Step (b)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid Coast Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Restrained; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of spiderweb)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You conjure a mass of thick, sticky webbing at a point of your choice within range. The webs fill a 20-foot cube from that point for the duration. The webs are difficult terrain and lightly obscure their area.</p>
					<p>If the webs aren't anchored between two solid masses (such as walls or trees) or layered across a floor, wall, or ceiling, the conjured web collapses on itself, and the spell ends at the start of your next turn. webs layered over a flat surface have a depth of 5 feet.</p>
					<p>Each creature that starts its turn in the webs or that enters them during its turn must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, the creature is restrained as long as it remains in the webs or until it breaks free. A creature restrained by the webs can use its action to make a Strength check against your spell save DC. If it succeeds, it is no longer restrained.</p>
					<p>The webs are flammable. Any 5-foot cube of webs exposed to fire burns away in 1 round, dealing 2d4 fire damage to any creature that starts its turn in the fire.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Web</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid Underdark Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<label type="string">Mirror Image; IMAGES: 3</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Three illusory duplicates of yourself appear in your space. Until the spell ends, the duplicates move with you and mimic your actions, shifting position so it's impossible to track which image is real. You can use your action to dismiss the illusory duplicates.</p>
					<p>Each time a creature targets you with an attack during the spell's duration, roll a d20 to determine whether the attack instead targets one of your duplicates.</p>
					<p>If you have three duplicates, you must roll a6 or higher to change the attack's target to a duplicate. With two duplicates, you must roll an 8 or higher. With one duplicate, you must roll an 11 or higher.</p>
					<p>A duplicate's AC equals 10 + your Dexterity modifier. If an attack hits a duplicate, the duplicate is destroyed. A duplicate can be destroyed only by an attack that hits it.</p>
					<p>It ignores all other damage and effects. The spell ends when all three duplicates are destroyed.</p>
					<p>A creature is unaffected by this spell if it can't see, if it relies on senses other than sight, such as blindsight, or if it can perceive illusions as false, as with truesight.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mirror Image</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Trickery Domain, Druid Coast Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As you hold your hands with thumbs touching and fingers spread, a thin sheet of flames shoots forth from your outstretched fingertips. Each creature in a 15-foot cone must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 3d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>The fire ignites any flammable objects in the area that aren't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Burning Hands</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cone)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Light Domain, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Fiend), Monk, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<type type="string">force</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<tknimg type="token"></tknimg>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create three glowing darts of magical force. Each dart hits a creature of your choice that you can see within range. A dart deals 1d4 + 1 force damage to its target. The darts all strike simultaneously, and you can direct them to hit one creature or several.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the spell creates one more dart for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Missile</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Arcane Recovery</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pearl worth at least 100 gp and an owl feather)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You choose one object that you must touch throughout the casting of the spell. If it is a magic item or some other magic-imbued object, you learn its properties and how to use them, whether it requires attunement to use, and how many charges it has, if any. You learn whether any spells are affecting the item and what they are. If the item was created by a spell, you learn which spell created it.</p>
					<p>If you instead touch a creature throughout the casting, you learn what spells, if any, are currently affecting it.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Identify (R)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Knowledge Domain, Eldritch Knight, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">lightning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Lightning springs from your hand to deliver a shock to a creature you try to touch. Make a melee spell attack against the target. You have advantage on the attack roll if the target is wearing armor made of metal. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 lightning damage, and it can't take reactions until the start of its next turn.</p>
					<p>The spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Cantrip</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shocking Grasp</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<label type="string">Detect Magic; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic (R)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Flaming Sphere; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<tknbutton type="token"></tknbutton>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of tallow, a pinch of brimstone, and a dusting of powdered iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A 5-foot-diameter sphere of fire appears in an unoccupied space of your choice within range and lasts for the duration. Any creature that ends its turn within 5 feet of the sphere must make a Dexterity saving throw.</p>
					<p>The creature takes 2d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action, you can move the sphere up to 30 feet. If you ram the sphere into a creature, that creature must make the saving throw against the sphere's damage, and the sphere stops moving this turn.</p>
					<p>When you move the sphere, you can direct it over barriers up to 5 feet tall and jump it across pits up to 10 feet wide. The sphere ignites flammable objects not being worn or carried, and it sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flaming Sphere</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<preparedDomain type="number">0</preparedDomain>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Light Domain, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00018>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Daggers, darts, slings, quarterstaffs, light crossbows</name>
			</id-00001>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Half-Elf</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.half_elf@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<shifttoken type="token"></shifttoken>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<stats>
			<bigFoeCR type="number">0</bigFoeCR>
			<biggestDamage type="number">4</biggestDamage>
			<crits type="number">0</crits>
			<damage type="number">5</damage>
			<damageReceived type="number">40</damageReceived>
			<fumbles type="number">0</fumbles>
			<healing type="number">0</healing>
			<healingReceived type="number">17</healingReceived>
			<hits type="number">0</hits>
			<kills type="number">0</kills>
			<kos type="number">2</kos>
			<misses type="number">0</misses>
			<sessionbigFoeCR type="number">0</sessionbigFoeCR>
			<sessionbiggestDamage type="number">0</sessionbiggestDamage>
			<sessioncrits type="number">0</sessioncrits>
			<sessiondamage type="number">0</sessiondamage>
			<sessiondamageReceived type="number">0</sessiondamageReceived>
			<sessionfumbles type="number">0</sessionfumbles>
			<sessionhealing type="number">0</sessionhealing>
			<sessionhealingReceived type="number">0</sessionhealingReceived>
			<sessionhits type="number">0</sessionhits>
			<sessionkills type="number">0</sessionkills>
			<sessionkos type="number">0</sessionkos>
			<sessionmisses type="number">0</sessionmisses>
		</stats>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00027_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Skill Versatility</name>
				<source type="string">Half-Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency in two skills of your choice.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<source type="string">Half-Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can't put you to sleep.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
		</traitlist>
		<weapon>
			<critdicebonus>
			</critdicebonus>
			<critrange>
				<melee type="number">20</melee>
				<ranged type="number">20</ranged>
			</critrange>
		</weapon>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<ammo type="number">9</ammo>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">20</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Crossbow, Light</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 80/320), loading, two-handed</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00007</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00001>
		</weaponlist>
	</character>
</root>
