<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.1" release="7|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">27</age>
		<alignment type="string">Lawful Good</alignment>
		<background type="string">Folk Hero</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.folkhero@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">2</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">5</hdused>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<name type="string">Paladin</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.paladin@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">21</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">17</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">4</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">max2</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">18</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Queen of Summer</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">60</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">120</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">360</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">31</load>
			<max type="number">180</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">6984</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">14000</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rustic Hospitality</name>
				<source type="string">Folk Hero</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Since you come from the ranks of the common folk, you fit in among them with ease. You can find a place to hide, rest, or recuperate among other commoners, unless you have shown yourself to be a danger to them. They will shield you from the law or anyone else searching for you, though they will not risk their lives for you.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity (the vampire Count Strahd von Zarovich, for instance).</p>
					<p>Within the same radius, you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the hallow spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on Hands</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your paladin level x5. As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.</p>
					<p>This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style: Dueling</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<p><b>Great Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p><b>Protection</b></p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 2nd level, you have learned to draw on divine magic through meditation and prayer to cast spells as a cleric does. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the paladin spell list.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="reference.spelllists.paladin@DD PHB Deluxe">Paladin Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Paladin table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells. To cast one of your paladin spells of 1st level or higher, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of paladin spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the paladin spell list. When you do so, choose a number of paladin spells equal to your Charisma modifier + half your paladin level, rounded down (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots. For example, if you are a 5th-level paladin, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Charisma of 14, your list of prepared spells can include four spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell cure wounds, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells. You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of paladin spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your paladin spells, since their power derives from the strength of your convictions. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a paladin spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a holy symbol (found in chapter 5) as a spellcasting focus for your paladin spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Oath of the Ancients</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The Oath of the Ancients is as old as the race of elves and the rituals of the druids. Sometimes called fey knights, green knights, or horned knights, paladins who swear this oath cast their lot with the side of the light in the cosmic struggle against darkness because they love the beautiful and life-giving things of the world, not necessarily because they believe in principles of honor, courage, and justice. They adorn their armor and clothing with images of growing things-leaves, antlers, or flowers-to reflect their commitment to preserving life and light in the world.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.paladin.features.tenetsoftheancients3@DD PHB Deluxe">Tenets of the Ancients</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.paladin.features.oathspells_ancients_3@DD PHB Deluxe">Oath Spells (Ancients)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.paladin.features.channeldivinity_ancients_3@DD PHB Deluxe">Channel Divinity (Ancients)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.paladin.features.auraofwarding7@DD PHB Deluxe">Aura of Warding</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.paladin.features.undyingsentinel15@DD PHB Deluxe">Undying Sentinel</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.paladin.features.elderchampion20@DD PHB Deluxe">Elder Champion</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tenets of the Ancients</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of the Ancients</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The tenets of the Oath of the Ancients have been preserved for uncounted centuries. This oath emphasizes the principles of good above any concerns of law or chaos. Its four central principles are simple.</p>
					<p><b>Kindle the Light. </b>Through your acts of mercy, kindness, and forgiveness, kindle the light of hope in the world, beating back despair.</p>
					<p><b>Shelter the Light. </b>Where there is good, beauty, love, and laughter in the world, stand against the wickedness that would swallow it. Where life flourishes, stand against the forces that would render it barren.</p>
					<p><b>Preserve Your Own Light. </b>Delight in song and laughter, in beauty and art. If you allow the light to die in your own heart, you can't preserve it in the world.</p>
					<p><b>Be the Light. </b>Be a glorious beacon for all who live in despair. Let the light of your joy and courage shine forth in all your deeds.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Oath Spells (Ancients)</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of the Ancients</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain oath spells at the paladin levels listed.</p>
					<h>Oath of the Ancients Spells</h>
					<p><b>Paladin Level - Spell</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.ensnaringstrike@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 3rd - Ensnaring Strike</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.speakwithanimals@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 3rd - Speak with Animals</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.moonbeam@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 5th - Moonbeam</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.mistystep@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 5th - Misty Step</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.plantgrowth@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 9th - Plant Growth</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.protectionfromenergy@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 9th - Protection from Energy</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.icestorm@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 13th - Ice Storm</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.stoneskin@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 13th - Stoneskin</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.communewithnature@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 17th - Commune With Nature</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.treestride@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: 17th - Tree Stride</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity (Ancients)</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of the Ancients</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you take this oath at 3rd level, you gain the following two Channel Divinity options.</p>
					<p><b>Nature's Wrath. </b>You can use your Channel Divinity to invoke primeval forces to ensnare a foe. As an action, you can cause spectral vines to spring up and reach for a creature within 10 feet of you that you can see.</p>
					<p>The creature must succeed on a Strength or Dexterity saving throw (its choice) or be restrained. While restrained by the vines, the creature repeats the saving throw at the end of each of its turns. On a success, it frees itself and the vines vanish.</p>
					<p><b>Turn the Faithless. </b>You can use your Channel Divinity to utter ancient words that are painful for fey and fiends to hear. As an action, you present your holy symbol, and each fey or fiend within 30 feet of you that can hear you must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature is turned for 1 minute or until it takes damage.</p>
					<p>A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can't willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can't take reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there's nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</p>
					<p>If the creature's true form is concealed by an illusion, shapeshifting, or other effect, that form is revealed while it is turned.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Health</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 3rd level, the divine magic flowing through you makes you immune to disease.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Extra Attack</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 5th level, you can attack twice, instead of once, whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00013>
		</featurelist>
		<gender type="string">Female</gender>
		<height type="string">3</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">1</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">3</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">44</total>
			<wounds type="number">44</wounds>
		</hp>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">3</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">14</ac>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">400 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Medium armor offers more protection than light armor, but it also impairs movement more. If you wear medium armor, you add your Dexterity modifier, to a maximum of +2, to the base number from your armor type to determine your Armor Class.</p>
					<p>This armor consists of a fitted metal chest piece worn with supple leather. Although it leaves the legs and arms relatively unprotected, this armor provides good protection for the wearer's vital organs while leaving the wearer relatively unencumbered.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes (max 2)</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Breastplate</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Medium Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">20</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">2</ac>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A shield is made from wood or metal and is carried in one hand. Wielding a shield increases your Armor Class by 2. You can benefit from only one shield at a time.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shortsword</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shortbow</name>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 80/320), two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00005>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Halfling</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Sylvan</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00004>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">5</level>
		<name type="string">Ivy</name>
		<notes type="string">Her full name is Evelyn Ilesere</notes>
		<perception type="number">11</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00003>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<uses type="number">1</uses>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00003>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">4</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">2</max>
				<used type="number">2</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Restrained; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMGO: 1d6 piercing; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The next time you hit a creature with a weapon attack before this spell ends, a writhing mass of thorny vines appears at the point of impact, and the target must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be restrained by the magical vines until the spell ends. A Large or larger creature has advantage on this saving throw. If the target succeeds on the save, the vines shrivel away.</p>
					<p>While restrained by this spell, the target takes 1d6 piercing damage at the start of each of its turns. A creature restrained by the vines or one that can touch the creature can use its action to make a Strength check against your spell save DC. On a success, the target is freed.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>If you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ensnaring Strike(oath)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain the ability to comprehend and verbally communicate with beasts for the duration. The knowledge and awareness of many beasts is limited by their intelligence, but at minimum, beasts can give you information about nearby locations and monsters, including whatever they can perceive or have perceived within the past day. You might be able to persuade a beast to perform a small favor for you, at the DM's discretion.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speak with Animals(oath)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Nature Domain, Druid, Eldritch Invocations, Ranger</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (several seeds of any moonseed plant and a piece of opalescent feldspar)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A silvery beam of pale light shines down in a 5-foot radius, 40-foot-high cylinder centered on a point within range. Until the spell ends, dim light fills the cylinder. When a creature enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it is engulfed in ghostly flames that cause searing pain, and it must make a Constitution saving throw. It takes 2d10 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>A shapechanger makes its saving throw with disadvantage. If it fails, it also instantly reverts to its original form and can't assume a different form until it leaves the spell's light.</p>
					<p>On each of your turns after you cast this spell, you can use an action to move the beam 60 feet in any direction.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>when you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Moonbeam(oath)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Briefly surrounded by silvery mist, you teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space that you can see.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Misty Step(oath)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid Coast Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00003>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds(free hand)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">piercing, magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a silver needle)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Area of Effect: 1 creature</p>
					<p>Saving Throw: None</p>
					<p>You conjure a shimmering spear and throw it at one creature you can see.</p>
					<p>Make a ranged spell attack against the target creature. If it hits, the spear does 3d10 piercing damage and is treated as a magic weapon.</p>
					<p>Enhancement: For each spell slot used higher than 2nd level, the spear does an additional 1d10 damage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Elmekia Lance</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 ft.</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Paladin, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity (the vampire Count Strahd von Zarovich, for instance).</p>
					<p>Within the same radius, you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the hallow spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 3rd level, the divine magic flowing through you makes you immune to disease.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Health</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">5</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">Vocal</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on hands</name>
				<prepared type="number">5</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<shortdescription type="string">You can touch the target to heal him 5 HP per slot or remove a poison or disease using 5 slots</shortdescription>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<effect_target type="string">targets</effect_target>
						<label type="string">Turn the Faithless; Turned</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p><b>Turn the Faithless.</b></p>
					<p>You can use your Channel Divinity to utter ancient words that are painful for fey and fiends to hear. As an action, you present your holy symbol, and each fey or fiend within 30 feet of you that can hear you must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature is turned for 1 minute or until it takes damage.A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can't willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can't take reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there's nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</p>
					<p>If the creature's true form is concealed by an illusion, shapeshifting, or other effect, that form is revealed while it is turned.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Channel Divinity</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Turn the Faithless</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<label type="string">Restrained</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p><b>Nature's Wrath </b>. You can use your Channel Divinity to invoke primeval forces to ensnare a foe. As an action, you can cause spectral vines to spring up and reach for a creature within 10 feet of you that you can see.</p>
					<p>The creature must succeed on a Strength or Dexterity saving throw (its choice) or be restrained. While restrained by the vines, the creature repeats the saving throw at the end of each of its turns. On a success, it frees itself and the vines vanish.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Channel Divinity</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Nature's Wrath (range 10 ft.)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of the Ancients</specialization>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<effect_target type="string">targets</effect_target>
						<label type="string">Astral Vine; IFT: ALIGN (evil); ATK: 2; DMG: 2</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Astral Vine; DMGTYPE: magic</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a weapon)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Area of Effect: The weapon your are carrying</p>
					<p>Saving Throw: None</p>
					<p>You enchant your weapon temporally is considered magical and has a bonus to hit and damage depending on your alignment.</p>
					<p>Good (except neutral good): +2 vs. evil creatures</p>
					<p>Evil (except neutral evil): +2 vs. good creatures</p>
					<p>This enchantment is cumulative with those of the weapon. The weapon emits bright light in a 20-foot radius.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Astral Vine</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1d4; SAVE: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a sprinkling of holy water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You bless up to three creatures of your choice within range. Whenever a target makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bless</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Paladin</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 2d6 thunder; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The first time you hit with a melee weapon attack during this spell's duration, your weapon rings with thunder that is audible within 300 feet of you, and the attack deals an extra 2d6 thunder damage to the target. Additionally, if the target is a creature, it must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be pushed 10 feet away from you and knocked prone.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderous Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00019>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: One type of artisan's tools, vehicles (land)</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: All armor, shields</name>
			</id-00003>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Halfling (Lightfoot)</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.halfling@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Small</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">25</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">tokens/host/bichos/silverpaw_paladin_tok.png</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lucky</name>
				<source type="string">Halfling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you roll a 1 on an attack roll, ability check, or saving throw, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Halfling Nimbleness</name>
				<source type="string">Halfling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can move through the space of any creature that is of a size larger than yours.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Brave</name>
				<source type="string">Halfling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being frightened.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Naturally Stealthy</name>
				<source type="string">Lightfoot</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can attempt to hide even when you are obscured only by a creature that is at least one size larger than you.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Shortsword</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00003</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ammo type="number">7</ammo>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">20</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Shortbow</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00004</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00005</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">1</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00005</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00004>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">48</weight>
	</character>
</root>
